Linxi WANG

Master student @ HCID (Human Computer Interaction Design)

Université Paris-Sud, Paris | +33 6 62 88 32 49 linxiwang7@gmail.com

About me

Design & Coding Skills

I am interested in HCID related work. UX/UI designer, Usability engineer, Interactive systems engineer, front-end developer...

For the year of 2018 I can start work from May(or Monday, 30 April, 2018) to late August.

I am a master student majoring in HCID, and interested in finding problems and solving them, which also reflects on the projects I did in the past year. As a designer and a developer, row I am working on designing more natural and efficient interactions between human and machine. I have done projects about travelling, kids game, data visualisation, efficient tools and groupware tools. I am enthusiastic, fast-learning, and curious, also playing an important role in team work.

UI/UX Design

From research, interview and gathering ideas to design, prototyping, evaluation, then finally test out the product with users, iterating.

Photoshop

Poster, Logo design

Education

Master of Computer Science

2018 - 2019

Axure

Rapid Prototyping

KTH, Royal Institute of Technology

Human Computer Interaction Design(HCID)

2017 - 2018

Sketch

Rapid Prototyping

Master of Computer Science

Université Paris-Sud Human Computer Interaction Design (HCID)

Master of Computer Science EIT Digital Master School 2017 - 2019

3D modeling/Unity

2017 2013

AR/VR

HCID, innovation & entrepreneurship

Bachelor of Engineering 2013 - 2017

P5.js/Processing

HTML5/CSS3/JavaScript

Web developing

Web Sketching

Jilin University

Electronic Information Engineering

Work experience

2016 - 2017

2015 - 2016

Develop Engineer (Intern)

Migu Digital Media of China Mobile Communications Corporation

- Learned Java programming, HTML5 and other knowledge
- Completed the interface design and programming work of Migu reading App's capture packet analysis software
- Involved in the development of Web APP, and programmed parts of html, css, JavaScript code according to the design chart of user experience designers
- User Experience design

Data Analyse

lava

Small tools developing

Hardware Develop Engineer (Intern)

Ningbo Topit Intelligent Technology Co. Ltd.

- Grasped the Altium Designer software to draw PCB circuit board, and hardware circuit diagram.
- Prepared corresponding programs of various module functions of automatic acquiring-bill machine on the Keil software

Language

English, Chinese

